# Dr. Dinh Duc Nha Nguyen (TONY) - Research Fellow

I have published eight papers, including six in Q1 journals as the first author in top-tier venues such as TDSC, and one in a B-ranked conference. I have mentored students to publish a high-impact paper and contributed to an Elsevier book chapter. I have received multiple awards for academic excellence, secured a successful grant application, and won an international prize. My teaching roles have been highly rated, with positive feedback from students. I also have extensive experience working with industry partners. My expertise lies in cybersecurity, AI technology, network security, and quantum technology, particularly in machine learning and data science.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

6.2023 - 11.2024**DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)** 

2.2022 - 6.2023**DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)** 

8.2017 - 2.2018TECH JDI (VIETNAM)

3.2013 - 2.2017TMA SOLUTIONS (VIETNAM)

#### ASSOCIATE RESEARCH FELLOW

Industry project: implement automatically hybrid Quantum Cryptography (PQC) in digital signature in Virtual Private Network.

#### RESEACH ASSISTANT & TUTOR

- Conducted experiments and worked on publications for multiple projects in AI technology (machine learning models) and cybersecurity (IoT, IDS...).
- Taught three subjects in cybersecurity.

## SENIOR TEST ENGINEER

Delivered V-key platform, resulting in savings of 98K €.

#### TEST ANALYST & NETWORKING SPECIALIST

- Designed and executed test scenarios, test cases, and automated test scripts.
- Set up and configured the network topology for lab.

### **EDUCATION HISTORY**

10.2020 - 6.2024**DEAKIN UNIVERSITY (AUSTRALIA)** 

#### DOCTOR OF PHILOSOPHY (CYBERSECURITY)

Award: School of Information Technology 2022 Student Excellence Award Higher Degree Research.

7.2018 - 7.2020**OUEENSLAND UNIVERSITY OF** TECHNOLOGY (AUSTRALIA)

## MASTER OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (NETWORKS)

Award: Awarded Dean's List for excellent academic performance in semester 2 in 2019 and semester 1 in 2020.

## TEACHING EXPERIENCES (DEAKIN UNIVERSITY)

- Cyber Security Management (Satisfaction 100% with comments from students). More.
- Cyber Security Analytics (Satisfaction 100% with comments from students).
- Advanced network Security (Satisfaction 92.9% with comments from students).

### INTERNATIONAL PRIZE

I have received Third Place in the 2022 Country to Country (C2C) Cybersecurity Challenge hosted by MIT, recognizing my skills in an international cybersecurity competition.

#### **PUBLICATIONS & MENTORSHIP**

Visit my Google Scholar Profile and IEEE Profile for a complete list of publications (9 papers). I have mentored students to publish a high-impact paper (IEEE TIFS) and another student to publish an Elsevier book chapter (preliminary acceptance).

CONTACT

Email: ndducnha@gmail.com Phone: (+61) 045 254 2713 Website: tonynguyen.work

